[{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Who played the role of Ernie McCracken, Roys nemesis, in the movie Kingpin?", "correct_answer": "Bill Murray", "incorrect_answers": ["Jeff Daniels", "Jack Black", "Ben Stiller"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In the movie Team America: World Police, who visits Kim Jong Ils mansion in search of weapons of mass destruction?", "correct_answer": "Hans Blix", "incorrect_answers": ["Dick Cheney", "Bill Clinton", "Saddam Hussein"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "How many recognized giraffe subspecies exist?", "correct_answer": "9", "incorrect_answers": ["6", "7", "5"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What two continents did Smilodon inhabit?", "correct_answer": "North and South America", "incorrect_answers": ["Europe and Asia", "Europe and Africa", "Asia and Africa"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which Star Wars villain has green and blue lightsabers?", "correct_answer": "General Grievous", "incorrect_answers": ["Emperor Palpatien", "Darth Maul", "Jango Fett"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "An insulator is a thin metal strip mounted in a holder. When too much current passes through  it, the metal strip melts and opens the circuit.", "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In 1984 what famous mogul offered a $100,000 reward for proof of the continued existence of Thylacines?", "correct_answer": "Ted Turner", "incorrect_answers": ["Donald Trump", "Rupert Murdock", "Bill Gates"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which one of these women is a sculptor famous for works with war-related themes?", "correct_answer": "Renee Headings", "incorrect_answers": ["Lin Mae Wang", "Lisa Picard", "May Howard  Jackson"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What is the minimum value of the function y= x^2+3x-1?", "correct_answer": "-13/4", "incorrect_answers": ["13/4", "-3/2", "3/2"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "This Czech writer wrote a play called  R.U.R.: Rossums Universal Robots.", "correct_answer": "Karel Capek", "incorrect_answers": ["Carl Kuchik", "Peter Kipchak", "Wilhem Capok"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Three dogs and two puppies weigh 128 lbs. Four dogs and three puppies weigh 176 lbs. All dogs weigh the same and all puppies weigh the same. What is the weight of two dogs and one puppy?", "correct_answer": "80 lbs", "incorrect_answers": ["32 lbs", "16 lbs", "48 lbs"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Name the Star Wars character who said: Search your feelings. You know it to be true.", "correct_answer": "Darth Vader", "incorrect_answers": ["Obi Wan Kenobi", "Yoda", "Emperor Palpetine"]}]